Marching to the New Wonderland
Ant Express
Delivering the Energy Seed is exhausting.
Need to mail a package? Come this way!
We are Ant Express!
No matter what is delivered or where it’s delivered,
we will deliver it for you swiftly and safely.
Need a delivery? Contact us.
“All missions, all finished” is our motto.
Why are you guys falling for these scammy ads?
Who’s there?
You have a delivery.
They’re here.
My ice cream didn’t even melt en route.
They’re so fast!
My wooden tower didn’t even fall en route.
They’re so stable!
My spider web hair clip is still intact.
Ant Express is awesome!
Wait,
I can just have the Energy Seed delivered to the Big Tree’s Summit.
Hello, how can I help you?
I need something delivered.
I’m worried that you won’t be able to get there, though.
Never fear! We at Ant Express can deliver parcels
to any place in the world.
Great!
Please deliver this to the Big Tree’s Summit for me.
I’m sorry, we can’t deliver parcels to the Big Tree’s Summit.
Why not?
Didn’t your ads say that you can deliver to anywhere?
That place is very dangerous.
It’s against Ant Express regulations to go there.
I knew it. Ant Express is a fraud.
Need to make a delivery?
Are you really willing to deliver it?
I was told that you can’t go there.
I mean, I’ve never heard of a place
where we ants can’t go to.
Leave it to me. I’ll get it done.
Are you sure? This is a very important parcel.
Don’t worry. Here at Ant Express, “all missions, all finished”.
I’m Andy. This is my work ID.
Then I’ll leave it to you, Andy.
I’m Paddi. Tell me once it’s been delivered, okay?
Hang in there!
He’s so professional. I don’t need to worry.
Once my boss gets to see my skills,
I’ll become a permanent Ant Express courier.
I’ll climb the ranks to general manager
and reach the pinnacle of life.
I guess I can stop for a snack first.
—Andy?　—Paddi?
Weren’t you delivering my parcel?
What are you doing here?
Well… Uh…
I get it.
We need to eat before working, right?
Right.
Here, have some.
Thanks!
I’ll be on my way now.
I’m so full.
I’ll take a nap first.
Andy?
Weren’t you delivering my parcel?
Why were you sleeping here?
Uh…
I get it.
We need to sleep to regain energy, right?
Yes, that’s right.
I won’t disturb you, then.
I’ll head back.
Let me know when it’s done!
Where’s my parcel?
Paddi!
Andy?
Did you really deliver the Energy Seed
to the Big Tree’s Summit already?
You people at Ant Express are truly something else!
I haven’t delivered it yet.
What?
Why haven’t you?
Where’s the Energy Seed?
I lost it.
What?
Aren’t you a master courier?
How did you lose it?
Actually, I’m just an intern.
I haven’t delivered a single parcel yet.
I saw that no one was delivering your parcel,
so I decided to give it a go,
and…
This is bad.
I need to find the Energy Seed!
Paddi,
listen.
Shut up!
Hey, listen to me!
No! I’m never trusting you again!
Fine.
I just wanted to tell you that there’s a chasm up ahead.
Why didn’t you say so?
I’ve found signs of the Energy Seed!
Paddi,
I’ll make sure to get it back for you.
Well, I’m not trusting you.
Where did Paddi go?
What’s going on with Sirius?
Who dumped this litter here?
The Energy Seed?
Nice! That was too easy!
Oh no.
We can’t let Wolffy take the Energy Seed.
I’ll ask for it back.
Keep your head down. I’ll think of something myself.
Am I really unable to open it without the goats’ handprints?
I refuse to believe
that I can’t open you without handprints.
What’s the matter?
Shh. I’m trying to think.
What in the world is this box made of?
I can’t think of anything.
If only Weslie were here.
I’ll help you get it back.
No, don’t go!
Give back my parcel.
Finders keepers, losers weepers! Hands off!
No. I’m never losing a parcel ever again.
Hands off. Now.
Look out, Andy!
You’ve come as well, Paddi?
Let him go!
We can talk about this, Mr. Ant.
How do I use this thing?
What’s this button for?
I’ll be back!
Andy,
why didn’t you let go of the box back there?
Because I’ve always dreamed
of becoming a dedicated Ant Express courier.
For the sake of Ant Express,
I can’t lose a parcel again.
I stopped trusting you, though.
I’m sorry.
I mean,
I’d have loved to deliver your parcel to the Big Tree’s Summit,
but I almost lost it.
I’m sorry.
I’m a failed courier.
But didn’t you get it back to me again, anyway?
To me,
you’re already an outstanding courier.
Thank you, Paddi!
No one has ever been so kind to me before.
I think we’re quite similar, actually.
I hope we can meet again.
We have branches all throughout the Big Tree.
I’m sure we’ll meet again.
Yeah.
There you are, Paddi.
It’s time to get going.
I’m coming!
Until next time, Andy.
It’s Auntie Ant calling.
Hello, Auntie Ant?
Andy,
congratulations on becoming a permanent Ant Express courier!
From now on, you may deliver parcels.
END